("I TOUCH MYSELF" BY DIVINYLS)
♪ I LOVE MYSELF ♪
♪ I WANT YOU TO LOVE ME ♪
♪ WHEN I FEEL DOWN ♪
♪ I WANT YOU ABOVE ME ♪
♪ I SEARCH MYSELF ♪
♪ I WANT YOU TO FIND ME ♪
♪ I FORGET MYSELF ♪
♪ I WANT YOU TO REMIND ME ♪
♪ I DON'T WANT ANYBODY ELSE ♪
♪ WHEN I THINK ABOUT
YOU, I TOUCH MYSELF ♪
♪ OH, I DON'T WANT
ANYBODY ELSE ♪
♪ OH NO, OH NO, OH NO ♪
♪ YOU'RE THE ONE WHO
MAKES ME COME RUNNIN' ♪
♪ YOU'RE THE SUN
WHO MAKES ME SHINE ♪
♪ WHEN YOU'RE AROUND,
I'M ALWAYS LAUGHIN' ♪
♪ I WANT TO MAKE YOU MINE ♪
♪ I CLOSE MY EYES AND
SEE YOU BEFORE ME ♪
♪ THINK I WOULD DIE IF
YOU WERE TO IGNORE ME ♪
♪ A FOOL COULD SEE JUST
HOW MUCH I ADORE YOU ♪
♪ I'D GET DOWN ON MY KNEES ♪
♪ I'D DO ANYTHING FOR YOU ♪
♪ I DON'T WANT ANYBODY ELSE ♪
♪ WHEN I THINK ABOUT
YOU, I TOUCH MYSELF ♪
♪ OH, I DON'T WANT
ANYBODY ELSE ♪
♪ OH NO, OH NO, OH NO ♪
♪ YEAH ♪
♪ I LOVE MYSELF ♪
♪ I WANT YOU TO LOVE ME ♪
♪ WHEN I FEEL DOWN ♪
♪ I WANT YOU ABOVE ME ♪
♪ I SEARCH MYSELF ♪
♪ I WANT YOU TO FIND ME ♪
♪ I FORGET MYSELF ♪
♪ I WANT YOU TO REMIND ME ♪
♪ I DON'T WANT ANYBODY ELSE ♪
♪ WHEN I THINK ABOUT
YOU, I TOUCH MYSELF ♪
♪ OH, I DON'T WANT
ANYBODY ELSE ♪
♪ OH NO, OH NO, OH NO ♪
♪ I WANT YOU ♪
♪ I DON'T WANT ANYBODY ELSE ♪
♪ AND WHEN I THINK ABOUT
YOU, I TOUCH MYSELF ♪
♪ OH ♪
♪ OH, OH ♪
♪ AH, AH, AH, AH, OH, AH ♪
♪ I DON'T WANT ANYBODY ELSE ♪
♪ WHEN I THINK ABOUT
YOU, I TOUCH MYSELF ♪
♪ OH, I DON'T WANT
ANYBODY ELSE ♪
♪ WHEN I THINK ABOUT
YOU, I TOUCH MYSELF ♪
♪ I TOUCH MYSELF ♪
♪ I HONESTLY DO ♪